客户无需报关就能欣赏自己的投资
The clients can view their investments without importing them,
这样就可以避税
so they avoid paying tax.
就像是艺术品中转站
It's sorta like a transit lounge for art?
艺术品  古董
Art, antiquities.
-任何值钱的东西  -任何东西
- Anything of value, really. - Anything?
只要合法就行
Anything legal.
但它和瑞士银行系统不无相似之处
But it's not unlike the Swiss banking system.
不透明
Opaque.
您肯定也明白  大部分自由港其实就是仓库
As I'm sure you are aware, most Freeports are just warehouses.
但我们保证您在这里可以真正享有...
But here we ensure that you can actually enjoy...
罗塔斯在奥斯陆自由港有些资产  我猜画在那里
Rotas has assets in the Oslo Freeport. I'm guessing it's there.
保险库在这边
And this way to the vaults!
你猜
Guessing?
她猜